{"classes":["PERSON","DATE","ORG","CARDINAL","GPE","TIME","NORP","LOC","WORK OF ART","ORDINAL","PERCENT"],"annotations":[["RT @JannyMedvedeva: Can I not ache after an episode 12? Can I just say... This is what I wanted all this time!!! #YuriOnIce12 https://t.co/…",{"entities":[[52,54,"CARDINAL"]]}],["@allieebrett whoa",{"entities":[]}],["@realDonaldTrump Like @JoeNBC said today, changing thinking may need the Stalin strategy, with Putin playing his pa… https://t.co/S9ysupSv90",{"entities":[[35,40,"DATE"],[73,79,"PERSON"],[95,100,"PERSON"]]}],["@JackJackJohnson what a babe 😍😍🔥💦",{"entities":[]}],["@buterafirefly @termiteking @Takeyiaa @harazustin rice beans lentils barley etc are the cheapest foods and they're all vegan FYI",{"entities":[]}],["Far and few between",{"entities":[]}],["@MEETtheBatman you're just lonely and hollow and needed a purpose in life.",{"entities":[]}],["@mahctekydnam do it",{"entities":[]}],["How can girls have 20 different things that they put on every day. I sometimes mix up the shampoo and conditioner. And that's just 2 things.",{"entities":[[19,21,"CARDINAL"],[131,132,"CARDINAL"]]}],["RT @datujoe143: @bea_viel88 @shejunki07 wher haha  YONG PAYTForLuckySun",{"entities":[]}],["RT @baz00per: she's been screaming at these water droplets for 3 fucking minutes get out of the shower you tiny moron https://t.co/rEw8V6SL…",{"entities":[[63,80,"TIME"]]}],["RT @WorldStarFunny: SAVAGE AF https://t.co/9zHcvjsWKA",{"entities":[]}],["Drawing underboobs in public  #MissionImpossible",{"entities":[]}],["RT @mnwild: ZUCKER! 10 seconds in! #mnwild goes up 1-0 against #nhljets. https://t.co/74jAHnPlAY",{"entities":[[20,30,"TIME"]]}],["Knock, knock! Who's there? Sam and Janet. Sam and Janet who? Sam and Janet Evening...",{"entities":[[27,30,"PERSON"],[35,41,"PERSON"],[42,45,"PERSON"],[50,55,"PERSON"],[61,64,"PERSON"],[69,74,"PERSON"],[75,82,"TIME"]]}],["RT @Seamless: RT by 5pm ET for a chance to win 1 of 10 Seamless picnic blankets! #SeamlessBecause takeout tastes better than PB&amp;J. http://t…",{"entities":[[20,26,"TIME"],[47,48,"CARDINAL"],[52,54,"CARDINAL"]]}],["The herd instinct among economists makes sheep look like independent thinkers.",{"entities":[]}],["What is your goal? — to live a happy life https://t.co/QQhSn0mV9A",{"entities":[]}],["Bidinishandbags https://t.co/rMJFg435Lj",{"entities":[]}],["Its kinda ironic, no?  White people say Asians look the same.   Asians say White people look the same.",{"entities":[[23,35,"NORP"],[40,46,"NORP"],[64,70,"NORP"],[75,87,"NORP"]]}],["Sometimes its ok to break the rule  YONG PAYTForLuckySun",{"entities":[]}],["RT @Ari1DsFan: \"What is it like being in the one direction fandom?\"  I don't regret a thing ! #BBMAs http://t.co/393moCU1Zw",{"entities":[[45,58,"WORK OF ART"]]}],["youre always welcome anak https://t.co/r5GYtBUzV0",{"entities":[]}],["@BOBBi_DEAN I always get hot salsa when I eat Mexican food.  lol",{"entities":[[46,53,"NORP"]]}],["User:NathanBishop https://t.co/WznA2p3tYX",{"entities":[]}],["@OnlyKehns take a photo and post it on twitter and claim she is one my festive meals",{"entities":[[39,46,"ORG"]]}],["User:Nationalchampion https://t.co/ProQA0qJnL",{"entities":[]}],["I wanna make toys too!   Call me Azfar the Farfeteer.",{"entities":[[33,52,"PERSON"]]}],["Joe: Democratic Party has ‘collapsed’ https://t.co/OrtpMnfGZC via @msnbc GOP presidents  since 1960.......Crooks, lairs, war mongers!!!",{"entities":[[0,3,"PERSON"],[5,21,"ORG"],[73,76,"ORG"],[95,99,"DATE"]]}],["Horrifying, and True: A Marketing AAAAAIIIGH! via Sohnen-Moe Associates | http://t.co/1zS5m60Vbx",{"entities":[[50,71,"ORG"]]}],["Smile Dental Clinics https://t.co/52AkL81OvC",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"]]}],["@moimori later. Once I have a better state of mind (nervous esok final exam tak habis study lagi.)",{"entities":[]}],["I have a 14 hour day tomorrow and half of it is on the surgical ward excuse me while I weep.",{"entities":[[9,20,"TIME"],[21,29,"DATE"]]}],["this is so funny i KNOW https://t.co/B41AbBNURM",{"entities":[]}],["RT @DoveCameron: what is dc1 and why is everyone tweeting me about it",{"entities":[]}],["RT @YONGforHASHTAGS: Keep sending your tweets  YONG OurFourthLuckySun",{"entities":[]}],["Savoring #positive #emotions: https://t.co/PBrbURybaE",{"entities":[]}],["The Last Taboo: Breaking Down the Stigma of Depression – http://t.co/uPNETiCH1V (blog) | Depression Treatments | http://t.co/YTISX9Yixn",{"entities":[[0,54,"WORK OF ART"]]}],["Maura Scanlan is now following me on Twitter! Thank you Maura Scanlan! Say hello anytime, … https://t.co/0wGwDdEYVt https://t.co/A5lnDTfuIk",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[37,44,"ORG"],[56,69,"PERSON"]]}],["@LouisGolia @JoeNBC @realDonaldTrump @MariaBartiromo  ONE DAY JOE LIKE THE OLD DAYS! GREAT! BUT YOUR ALREADY BACK O… https://t.co/awtdjYSXeZ",{"entities":[[54,61,"TIME"],[62,65,"PERSON"]]}],["Way to go evangelicals .......44% of EV's voted for Trump! 50% of GOP favor Putin!!!!   Swamps??? We have one in ev… https://t.co/TD2hZjjHSP",{"entities":[[10,22,"NORP"],[29,33,"PERCENT"],[52,57,"PERSON"],[59,62,"PERCENT"],[66,69,"ORG"],[76,81,"PERSON"]]}],["Ruby Wax: the reason why mindfulness may be the secret to some happy brand new year | Overcome Depression | http://t.co/YWydfsl3Nd",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[79,83,"TIME"]]}],["Eminem Goes To 2k And Back again At Uncommon New York Display | Southern Park Shows Pictures | http://t.co/YrZaYDoPmT",{"entities":[[0,6,"PERSON"],[45,53,"GPE"],[64,92,"ORG"]]}],["User:Toptenpackers https://t.co/nwzcEFIIcs",{"entities":[]}],["This is Tallahassee. https://t.co/S4eDrDlKRH",{"entities":[[8,20,"GPE"]]}],["It's Sunday, I need a break, so I'm planning to spend as little time as possible on the #A14...",{"entities":[[5,11,"DATE"]]}],["@assnips big cities are way more social, that's for sure",{"entities":[]}],["@iAmAustinJones hey. Since you are a fellow member of the 5sosfam you have an obligation to tweet #MTVFanWars5SOSFam thank you. PS you're 👍❤",{"entities":[[58,65,"ORG"]]}],["@PrincessAsh1ey how do you make sufficient money to support yourself then?",{"entities":[]}],["RT @J_Rosenfield: find someone who looks at you the way Hideo Kojima looks at spaghetti. https://t.co/JOCHF2IKB9",{"entities":[[56,68,"PERSON"]]}],["@MissLusyd oh yeah. That too.",{"entities":[]}],["Hey KiltronX Enviro thanks for the follow!",{"entities":[[4,19,"PERSON"]]}],["RT @GMWWriters: I just officially got the call, and would like to thank this audience for its incredible love and loyalty. Please watch our…",{"entities":[]}],["@BbMrsbrownsboys Rory's Botox episode was hilarious, especially when Mammy thought Kathy's boss was Rory, I near choked laughing 😂😂😂",{"entities":[[17,21,"PERSON"],[69,74,"PERSON"],[83,90,"PERSON"],[100,104,"PERSON"]]}],["@tehaumaster graduated tehaum is the goat wow",{"entities":[[23,29,"PERSON"]]}],["The best part about hitting rock bottom is that there's only one way to go... up",{"entities":[]}],["@dauspozi its actually a glowing dildo but sokay. You tried.",{"entities":[]}],["RT @5SOSTumblrx: i feel like with SGFG Michael is going to shine through 100x more than he did on the first album and i can't fucking wait",{"entities":[[39,46,"PERSON"],[73,77,"CARDINAL"],[102,107,"ORDINAL"]]}],["RT @iamdjmdot: This is why @edsheeran is one of my favorites. Pure talent #BBMAs",{"entities":[]}],["@thehill This duffus is in tall weeds!  Dumb, Stupid, Evil but beyond that a semi-narcissist golfer! https://t.co/MNsmLu7rkK",{"entities":[]}]]}